<resources>
    <string name="app_name">News Companion</string>
    <string name="category_space">Space</string>
    <string name="title_activity_news_article">NewsArticle</string>
    <string name="article_image">Main Image of Article</string>
    <string name="read_on_guardian">Read on The Guardian</string>
    <string name="loading_image">Loading Image Progress</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="preference_articles_number">Number of Articles</string>
    <string name="preference_articles_number_key">page-size</string>
    <string name="preference_articles_number_default">10</string>

    <string name="preference_order_by_key">order-by</string>
    <string name="preference_order_by_newest">newest</string>
    <string name="preference_order_by_oldest">oldest</string>
    <string name="preference_order_by_relevance">relevance</string>

    <string name="preference_order_by_key_label">Order BY</string>
    <string name="preference_order_by_newest_label">Newest</string>
    <string name="preference_order_by_oldest_label">Oldest</string>
    <string name="preference_order_by_relevance_label">Relevance</string>

    <string name="no_internet_connection">We detected that you are currently not connected to the internet.
    Please re-connect to view latest news articles.</string>
    <string name="space_description">Ever fantasized by the enormous universe around us or wanted to
        venture out deep inside it? We shall try to satisfy your curiosity with the latest discoveries
        and news about the Space.</string>
    <string name="tech_description">The world of technology is too deep to dive in. You may easily
        sink down. We will keep you afloat and updated with the world of tech.</string>
    <string name="physics_description">Physics is the natural science that studies matter and its behavior
        through space and time. Keep yourself updated with discoveries about all aspects of nature
        on both the macroscopic and submicroscopic levels.</string>
    <string name="environment_description">The alarm has rung. Its now or never. We need to act immediately
        to protect our environment. Keep yourself updated about the latest developments about the effects
        of human actions on environment and raise your voice.</string>
    <string name="business_description">In this shrewd world of business, you cannot afford to be outdated.
    Keep up to the latest industry standards, policies and much more with us.</string>
    <string name="empty_data">Everything isn\'t right. Either there is some problem on our or your end.
        If that is not the case, something even worse has happened. <b>We may have run out of articles.</b>
    But that should not be the case, how about refreshing the app or wait some time. Anyways, if your patience give up you
    can always contact us. We will be more than happy to help.</string>
</resources>
